<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Volta Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="attractions_tab">ATTRACTIONS</string>
    <string name="hotels_tab">HOTELS</string>
    <string name="landmarks_tab">LANDMARKS</string>
    <string name="image_of_place">Image of Place</string>
    <string name="afadzato_description">Mount Afadja, known in the Ewe language as Afadjoto, is the highest mountain in Ghana. The summit of this peak is located near the border with Togo, in the Volta Region of Ghana, close to the village of Liati Wote in Afadzato South District. Part of the Agumatsa sub-range of the West Africa Mountains, its summit is 885 metres (2,904 ft) above sea level.</string>
    <string name="lake_volta_description">With a storage capacity of 124,000,000 acre-feet of water, Lake Volta is one of the largest man-made lakes in the world. It is about 250 miles (400km) long and covers 3,283 square miles (8,502 square km), or 3.6 percent of Ghana’s area. The estuary is an area of great scenic beauty with river and ocean beaches, and picnic spots shaded by palm tree. The sand bars are the nesting grounds for sea birds, and endangered species.</string>
    <string name="wli_description">Wli Falls are situated in the heart of a tropical forest, 20km from Hohoe. Wli is the highest waterfall in Ghana and is fed year-round by the waters of the Agumatsa River. Reaching the falls is fun and adventure-filled. You must cross 11-log bridges which span the meandering river before arriving at the falls. Besides the spectacular view, your reward is the brisk, refreshing water which is great for swimming and makes an excellent natural cooler for your beer. Thousands of bats make their home among the cliffs which surround the falls.</string>
    <string name="tafi_description">Tafi Atome is surrounded by an indigenous tropical forest with very high floral concentration. In this forest, one could find the endangered, playful and rather sacred True Mona Monkeys.  Believing the monkeys to be messengers to the gods and their protectors, the chiefs and people of Tafi have been protecting them for the past 200 years. Hundreds of speicies of monkeys, including the nearly extinct Mona, make the dense tropical forest around Tafi Atome their home. Tradition does not permit people to kill or harm them.</string>
    <string name="volta_serene_description">Volta Serene Hotel in Ghana is the only four-star facility located in the heart of the regional capital, Ho. The hotel sits atop the picturesque Kabakaba Hill in Ho and our panoramic terraces provide the most magnificent views of the Ho township. The intimate atmosphere of the hotel gives guests the comforts of a private home. Whether you’re staying for business or leisure, Volta Serene Hotel in Ghana makes sure that you get nothing less than the best that the capital can offer.</string>
    <string name="sogakope_description">Sogakope Beach Resort is more than just an elegant beach resort, it is the pride of Sogakope in the Volta Region of Ghana and its set in a rich and tranquil gardens with the famous Volta River on its doorstep.  Where indulgence meets relaxation, this new purpose built resort offers a peaceful and relaxed lifestyle in a well-designed grounds and facilities with a true African feel yet modern.</string>
    <string name="akosombo_hotel_description">Volta Hotel Akosombo is definitely a haven of comfort, hospitality, and natural beauty.  The hotel provides a fantastic view of the lake, dam, and adjoining mountain slope. It offers Standard and Twin Rooms, as well as Private Villas and Executive Suites. Each dwelling gives a vibe of sophisticated elegance and complete relaxation. This comes courtesy of our high-quality furnishing and amenities.</string>
    <string name="akosombo_description">Akosombo Dam is a rock-fill dam on the Volta River, near Akosombo, Ghana, completed in 1965 as part of the Volta River Project. Its construction was jointly financed by the government of Ghana, the World Bank, the United States, and the United Kingdom. The dam rises 440 feet (134 m) above ground level and has a crest 2,201 feet (671 m) wide and a volume of 10,451,000 cubic yards (7,991,000 cubic m). The dam impounds Lake Volta; this huge reservoir has a capacity of 124,000,000 acre-feet (153,000,000,000 cubic m) and is used for commercial fishing and navigation. The large electric-power-generating capacity (912 megawatts) of the Akosombo Dam meets Ghana’s needs and provides a surplus for sale to neighbouring countries.</string>
    <string name="mt_afadza">Mount Afadja</string>
    <string name="wli_fall">Wli Waterfall</string>
    <string name="tafi_atome">Tafi Atome Monkey Sanctuary</string>
    <string name="volta_serene">Volta Serene Hotel</string>
    <string name="volta_akosombo">Volta Hotel Akosombo</string>
    <string name="soga_beach">Sogakope Beach Resort</string>
    <string name="lake_volta">Lake Volta</string>
    <string name="akosombo_dam">Akosombo Dam</string>
    <string name="festivals_tab">Festivals</string>
    <string name="asogli_festival">Asogli Te Za (Yam Festival)</string>
    <string name="asogli_description">Asogli Yam Festival is an annual festival celebrated by the people of Asogli in the Ho Municipality located in the Volta Region of Ghana. It is celebrated in September annually to celebrate the cultivation of yam that was started by a hunter who found the tuber in the forest during his hunting expedition. According to history, the cultivation of yam among the people of Asogli started when the yam that the hunter hid during his hunting expedition later germinated and grew bigger. The celebration was brought into Ghana by the Ewe people of Ghana when they migrated from Notse in the Republic of Togo; where it is still celebrated.</string>
    <string name="hogbotso">Hogbetsotso Festival</string>
    <string name="hogbetsotso_description">The Hogbetsotso festival is celebrated by the chiefs and people of Anlo in the Volta region of Ghana. The festival is celebrated annually on the first Saturday in the month of November. The name of the festival is derived from the Ewe language and translates as, the festival of exodus, or "coming from Hogbe (Notsie)". The celebration of the festival was instituted about four decades ago.</string>
    <string name="kente">Kente Festival</string>
    <string name="kente_description">Every year, since 1995, the Agotime Kente Festival (Agbamevorza) has taken place in the town of Kpetoe, in Ghana’s Volta. The festival has been celebrated to showcase the uniqueness of Kente as a matchless indigenous fabric from Ghana. Also, it is to draw attention to the aesthetic and cultural values of the Kente cloth.</string>
</resources>
